James Earle and Laura Gardin Fraser Papers
James Earle and Laura Gardin Fraser Papers
- Memorabilia
  - General
    - Fraser, James Earle and Laura Gardin
      - Audiorecordings
        - [Untitled Fraser Tape #13], fraser_je_041; 1/4 inch audio tape (Oversize 26)
          Side 1: In the Blue of the Evening; It’s Always You; Whispering; Two in Love; The Sunny Side of the Street; Boogie Woogie; Hawaiian War Chant; Frenesi; Chat Chao Chao; When Johnny Comes Marching Home; Sunset to Sunrise; Sentimental Journey; Helpless; I Know Why; Along the Santa Fe Trail; Midnight on the Trail; Where the Mountains Meets the Sky; I Come Here to Talk for Joe; Daybreak; There Are Such Things; You Are Never Away; Side 2: Be Careful It’s My Heart; Someone to Watch Over Me; The Man I Love; If I Loved You; Goodbye Sue; I’m Gonna Love That Gal; My Best to You; Anniversary Song; My Heart Sings; What a Sweet Surprise; Love Walked In; Do It Again; Mad About Him; Blues in the Night; Birth of the Blues; The Waiter; You’re Just in Love; Marrying for Love; I’ll String Along With You; Powder Your Face Sunshine; I Love the Guy
      - Newspaper clippings, 1931-1950 (Box 54)
    - Fraser and Tilton families
      - Genealogy (Box 55)
    - Gardin, Alice Tilton
      - Ephemera, 1940 (Box 55)
      - Newspaper clippings, 1939 (Box 55)
    - Gardin, John E.
      - Newspaper clippings, 1926 (Box 55)
    - Harding, Ann
      - Newspaper clippings, 1923-1937 (Box 55)
    - Robinson, Edwin Arlington
      - Ephemera, 1904-1933 (Box 55)
      - Newspaper clippings
        - Miscellaneous, 1920-1965 (Box 55)
        - Book reviews, 1920-1935 (Box 55)
        - Poetry, 1919 (Box 55)
      - Obituaries, 1935 (Box 55)
      - Scrapbook, undated (Box 55)
      - Scrapbook (oversize) (Oversize 5)
    - Saint-Gaudens, Augustus
      - Newspaper clippings, 1948 (Box 55)
    - Tilton, Theodore
      - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 55)
    - Unidentified
      - Blueprints and diagrams, undated (Box 55)
      - Notebooks, undated (Box 55)
      - Notebook, undated (Box 67)
  - Photographs
    - Miscellaneous, undated (Box 55)
    - Album, undated (Box 55)
    - Album (oversize) (Oversize 5)
    - Animals, undated (Box 55)
    - Cowboys, undated (Box 55)
    - Darling, Jay, undated (Box 56)
    - DeCoux, Janet, undated (Box 56)
    - Dogs, undated (Box 56)
    - Family and friends, ca.1880-1947; 5 folders (Box 56)
    - Family and friends, undated (Box 57)
      See also Glass negatives in Box 83.
    - Family and friends (oversize) (Oversize 3)
    - Fraser, Cora West, undated (Box 57)
    - Fraser, James Earle, ca.1894-1910; 2 folders (Box 57)
      See also Glass negatives in Boxes 83-84.
    - Fraser, James Earle (oversize) (Oversize 10)
    - Fraser, Laura Gardin, undated; 3 folders (Box 57)
    - Fraser, Laura Gardin, undated (Box 58)
    - Fraser, Laura Gardin (oversize) (Oversize 10)
    - Fraser, James Earle and Laura Gardin, undated (Box 58)
    - Gardin, Alice Tilton, undated (Box 58)
      See also Glass negatives in Box 84.
    - Harding, Ann, undated (Box 58)
    - Horses, undated; 3 folders (Box 58)
    - Horses, undated (Box 59)
    - Huntington, Anna Hyatt, undated (Box 59)
    - Moore, Charles, undated (Box 59)
    - National Achievement Awards, 1942-1948 (Box 59)
    - Robinson, Edwin Arlington, 1872-1933 (Box 59)
    - Robinson, Edwin Arlington (oversize), 1872-1933 (Oversize 3)
    - Rubins Family, undated (Box 59)
    - Saint-Gaudens' Studio, undated (Box 59)
    - Tilton, Alice, undated (Box 59)
    - Tilton, Theodore, undated (Box 59)
    - Views and Scenes
      - Slides in Lumiere box, undated (Box 67)
      - Miscellaneous, undated; 2 folders (Box 59)
      - Miscellaneous (oversize) (Oversize 8)
      - Europe, 1949; 3 folders (Box 60)
      - Latin America, undated (Box 60)
      - Pacific, 1949 (Box 60)
      - Paris, undated (Box 60)
      - Virginia, undated (Box 60)
      - Westport, Connecticut, undated; 2 folders (Box 60)
      - Yucatan, undated (Box 61)
      - Wheelwright, Joe, undated (Box 61)
  - Printed matter
    - Catalogues
      - "Charles Cary Rumsey", 1927 (Box 61)
      - "Small Bronzes by Great Sculptors as Prizes", 1926 (Box 61)
    - Magazine separates
      - "Michelangelo's Sistine Chapel," Life, 1949 (Box 61)
    - Newspaper
      - The Independent, XL, 1888 (Box 61)
    - Periodicals
      - "The Diagonal," I, 1920 (Box 61)
    - Pamphlets
      - "Hamlin Garland as West Salem Knew Him", 1951 (Box 61)
      - "Isaiah Bowman" by Gladys M. Wrigley, 1951 (Box 61)
      - "War" by Kerr Eby, undated (Box 61)
    - Postcards, undated; 2 folders (Box 61)
    - Postcards with inscriptions, 1909-1949; 2 folders (Box 67)
    - Postcards without inscriptions, undated; 2 folders (Box 67)
- Writings
  - Allen, Henry Butler
    - Article, "Franklin Touches Upon Presidential Authority and Morals in Politics," Franklin Institute News, XVII, 1952; published material (Box 61)
  - Faulkner, Barry
    - Article, "A Commemorative Tribute to James Earle Fraser", undated (Box 61)
  - Betts, Craven Langstroth
    - Verse, "To Edwin Arlington Robinson on His Fiftieth Birthday", undated (Box 61)
  - Fraser, James Earle
    - Articles
      - Fragments, undated (Box 61)
      - "Architectural Sculpture"
        - Draft, undated (Box 61)
        - Galley proofs, 1929 (Box 61)
        - Encyclopedia Britannica, 1929; published material (Box 61)
      - "Augustus Saint-Gaudens"
        - Drafts, undated (Box 61)
        - Century Association Hundredth Anniversary Exhibition Catalogue, undated; published material (Box 61)
      - "Akeley, the Sculpture," Natural History, 1927; published material (Box 61)
      - On Edwin Arlington Robinson, undated (Box 61)
      - On the buffalo nickel, undated (Box 61)
      - "Franklin's All-Pervading Curiosity," Dedication of the Benjamin Franklin Memorial, 1938; published material (Box 62)
      - "Frederick McMonnies"
        - Draft, undated (Box 62)
        - Commemorative Tributes...American Academy of Arts and Letters, 1939; published material (Box 62)
      - On Karl Anderson, undated (Box 62)
      - On Lincoln, undated (Box 62)
      - On the National Academy of Design, undated (Box 62)
      - On South Dakota Boyhood, ca. 1945 (Box 62)
      - "What Kind of War Memorial"
        - Drafts, undated (Box 62)
        - The Rotarian, 1946; published material (Box 62)
      - "Whitney's Polo Party", undated (Box 62)
    - Book, untitled autobiography, undated
      - I "Indian Prairie"
        - Fragments (Box 62)
        - Draft A (Box 62)
        - Drafts B-C and fragments (Box 62)
        - Drafts D-G (Box 62)
        - Drafts H-K (Box 63)
      - II "Minneapolis" (Box 63)
      - III "Beaux Arts" (Box 63)
      - IV "Italian Journey", drafts A-H (Box 63)
      - VIII "New York" (Box 63)
    - Diaries
      - [Vol. 1], 1929; says J.E. Fraser on front, but content (e.g., references to "Jay" and "Jimmy") suggests it may be Laura's diary (Box 63)
      - [Vol. 2], 1932; says J.E. Fraser on front, but content (e.g., references to "Jay" and "Jimmy") suggests it may be Laura's diary (Box 63)
      - [Vol. 3], 1949 (Box 63)
    - Films
      - Lincoln Memorial Group, undated; fraser_je_042; 16mm film, black and white, silent, 100 feet (Oversize 25)
      - Lincoln Circle Group, undated; fraser_je_043; 16mm film, black and white, silent, 100 feet (Oversize 25)
    - Interviews
      - WCVS; Chicago, Ill., 1941; phonodisc (Box 64)
      - WCVS; Chicago, Ill. (oversize), 1941; phonodisc; Transferred to Belfer Audio Archive 5/16/00
    - Notes
      - On Adolph Weinman, undated (Box 64)
      - On Charles Dana Gibson, undated (Box 64)
      - On Lee Laurie, undated (Box 64)
      - On modeling the bust of Theodore Roosevelt, undated (Box 64)
      - On Saint-Gaudens, undated (Box 64)
    - Speeches
      - On Benjamin Franklin, undated (Box 64)
      - On memorials, undated (Box 64)
      - National Academy and Institute of Arts and Letters, 1951 (Box 64)
      - "Why Sculpture?", 1958 (Box 64)
  - Fraser, James Earle and Laura Gardin
    - Interview
      - "Spotlight on Youth", 1947 (Box 64)
  - Fraser, Laura Gardin
    - Articles
      - "History of American Sculpture", 1959 (Box 64)
    - Diaries
      See also Writings: James Earle Fraser: Diaries for two volumes that may be Laura's.
      - [Vol. 4], 1931 (Box 64)
      - [Vol. 5], 1933 (Box 64)
      - [Vol. 6], 1934 (Box 64)
      - [Vol. 7], 1935 (Box 64)
      - Unbound fragments, 1964 (Box 65)
    - Films
      - "Patton Unveiling and Bridge Groups", undated; fraser_je_044; 16mm film, black and white, silent, 100 feet (Oversize 25)
      - "The Medal Maker", undated; fraser_je_045; 16mm film, black and white, silent, 300 feet (Oversize 25)
      - "Lee-Jackson Casting and Setting #2", undated; fraser_je_046; 16mm film, black and white, silent, 300 feet (Oversize 25)
    - Speeches
      - "On sculpture", 1958 (Box 65)
  - Gardin, Alice Tilton
    - Diaries, 1897-1898 (Box 65)
  - Gardin, Frieda
    - Article, "The Life of John E. Gardin", 1927; published material (Box 65)
  - Gardin, John E.
    - Articles
      - "Conditions in Foreign Countries", 1913; published material (Box 65)
      - "An Era of Financial History", 1915; published material (Box 65)
      - "The Future of International Finance", 1919; published material (Box 65)
      - "Liberty Bonds for the Business Woman", 1917; published material (Box 65)
      - "Protection of Our Gold Supply", 1913; published material (Box 65)
  - Hobson, Katherine T.
    - Article, "Laura Gardin Fraser.. .Seen Through Stars", National Sculpture Review, 1967; published material (Box 65)
  - Louchheim, Aline B.
    - Article, "Most Famous Unknown Sculpture", New York Times Magazine, 1951; published material (Box 65)
  - McAllister, Francis
    - Verse, To Ann Harding, 1925 (Box 65)
  - Moore, Charles
    - Articles
      - "Fine Arts Offer Brilliant Leadership in Education", University of Ohio News Bulletin, V, 1930; published material (Box 65)
      - "Personalities in Washington Architecture", 1937; published material (Box 65)
      - "Wakefield, the Birthplace of George Washington", undated (Box 65)
      - "Washington--City of Splendor", Current History, XXXII, 1930; published material (Box 66)
    - Speeches
      - "Adeline Adams, Author", 1930 (Box 66)
      - "Britain in War Time", undated (Box 66)
      - Phi Beta Kappa, undated (Box 66)
      - On the Twenty-Fifth Anniversary of the National Commission of Fine Arts, 1935 (Box 66)
      - Untitled, undated (Box 66)
  - Robinson, Edwin Arlington
    - Article, "The First Seven Years", 1930; page proofs, revised (Box 66)
    - Verse
      - "Cavender's House", undated; tsc. rev. (Box 66)
      - "Dionysus in Doubt" galley proof, 1925 (Box 66)
      - "The Man Who Died Twice"
        - Drafts A-C, 1922; undated; holographs, typescripts, some with revisions (Box 66)
        - Galley proofs, revised, 1924 (Box 66)
  - Seacrest, Effie
    - Article, "James Earle Fraser", The American Magazine of Art, undated; published material (Box 66)
  - Sterling, George
    - Verse, "His Own Country", 1921 (Box 66)
  - Tilton, Alice
    - Verse, On sleeping cars, undated (Box 66)
  - Tilton, Elizabeth
    - Diary [Vol. 8], 1876 (Box 66)
  - Unidentified
    - Articles
      - On the art of today, undated (Box 66)
      - "James Earle Fraser", The American Society Legion of Honor Magazine, 1954 (Box 66)
      - "James Earle Fraser's Sculptures in Bronze", The Metal Arts, undated (Box 66)
      - On monuments, undated (Box 66)
    - Notes, 1932-1953 (Box 66)
    - Speech, on Alice Morgan Wright, undated (Box 66)
- Glass negatives
  - Designs and reproductions
    - Fraser, James Earle
      - Medals
        - American Academy of Arts and Letters (Box 68)
        - American Institute of Graphic Arts (Box 68)
        - American Society of Mechanical Engineers (Box 68)
        - Comité Americain Pour les Regions Dévastés de la France (Box 68)
        - Harriman, Edward H. (Box 68)
        - New York State Spanish-American War (Box 68)
        - Peace of Versailles (Box 68)
        - Roosevelt, Theodore Memorial Association (Box 68)
        - Victory, World War I, 5 glass negatives (Box 68, 69)
        - Williams College (Box 69)
        - Yale University Howland Memorial (Box 69)
      - Sculpture
        - Albright, Joseph J. and Elizabeth, memorial (Box 69)
        - "Amazon" (Box 69)
        - "Aviator" (Box 69)
        - "Basque" (Box 69)
        - Brewster, Horatio Hathaway, relief; 2 glass plate negatives (Oversize 23)
        - "The Buffalo Prayer" (Box 69)
        - "Canadian Officer", 23 glass negatives (Box 69, 70)
        - Chase, J. Eastman, bust; 4 glass negatives (Box 70, 71)
        - "Cheyenne Warrior" (Box 71)
        - Chicago University Club, relief (Box 71)
        - Cleveland, Grover, memorial (Box 71)
        - "Dancer" (Box 71)
        - Delano, Warren, bust (Box 71)
        - Deming, E.W., bust (Box 71)
        - "End of the Trail" (Box 72)
        - "End of the Trail" (Oversize 27)
        - Ericson, David Barnard, relief (Oversize 27)
        - Ericsson, John, memorial; 18 glass negatives (Box 72, 73)
        - Evans, June, bust (Box 73)
        - Ford, Patrick, bust (Box 73)
        - Gibson, Charles Dana, bust (Box 73)
        - Hamilton, Alexander, standing figure; 13 glass negatives (Box 73, 74)
        - Hay, John, memorial (Box 74)
        - Indian, bust (Box 74)
        - Indian, standing figure (Box 74)
        - "Journey Through Life", 2 glass negative (Box 74, 75)
        - Key, Francis Scott, memorial (Box 75)
        - LeDoux, Louis, bust (Box 75)
        - Lincoln, Abraham, seated figure (Box 75)
        - Locke, George Lyman, relief; 2 glass negatives (Box 75)
        - Locke, George Lyman, relief; 2 glass negatives (Box 76)
        - Mask (Box 76)
        - Michigan Avenue Bridge, Chicago, pylons, "Discoverers" and "Pioneers" (Box 76)
        - Potter, Bishop Henry C., sarcophagus (Box 76)
        - "Priscilla" (Box 76)
        - Riley, John, bust (Box 76)
        - Roosevelt, Theodore, bust; 4 glass negatives (Box 76)
        - Roosevelt, Theodore, bust; 4 glass negatives (Box 77)
        - Roosevelt, Theodore, death mask (Box 77)
        - Roosevelt, Theodore, relief (Box 77)
        - Schoellkopf, Henry, relief (Case 10)
        - "Victory", 10 glass negatives (Box 77)
        - "Victory", 12 glass negatives (Box 78)
        - Whitney Children, busts, reliefs; 8 glass plate negatives (Oversize 23)
        - "Young Artist", bust (Box 78)
    - Fraser, Laura Gardin
      - Coin, Alabama Centennial half dollar (Box 78)
      - Medals
        - Belleau Wood Memorial Association (Box 78)
        - "Better Babies" (Box 79)
        - Bide-A-Wee Home for Dogs (Box 79)
        - "Doctrina" (Box 79)
        - Morgan Horse Club (Box 79)
        - Horse Association of America, polo (Box 79)
        - U.S. Army and Navy Chaplains (Box 79)
        - "Vermont" (Box 79)
      - Sculpture
        - Acadia Mountain Plaque (Box 79)
        - "Baby with Duck" (Box 79)
        - Dog, "Snuff" (Box 79)
        - Duck (Box 79)
        - "Goat Baby", statue (Box 79)
        - Golf Player, sundial (Box 79)
        - "Grape Baby", fountain (Box 80)
        - Holloway, Frances Angeline, relief (Box 80)
        - Horse, "Prince Friarstown" (Box 80)
        - "The Long Long Trail", relief (Box 80)
        - "Nymph and Satyr" (Box 80)
        - Russell Memorial (Box 80)
        - Smith, Rev. Cornelius B., relief (Box 80)
        - Smith, Eugene, bust (Box 80)
        - Stuart, Gilbert, bust (Box 80)
        - Urn with Polo Players (Box 81)
        - "Young Porker" (Box 81)
    - Fraser, James Earle and Laura Gardin
      - Medals, photographs and negatives (Box 81)
      - Sculpture
        - Models (Box 81)
        - Negatives, 3 glass negative (Box 81)
        - Negatives, 5 glass negative (Box 82)
    - Frémiet, E.
      - Sculpture (Box 82)
    - Olesen, Olaf
      - Paintings (Box 82)
    - Unidentified sculptures, 4 glass negative (Box 82, 83)
  - Memorabilia
    - Photographs
      - Family and friends (Case 16)
      - Fraser, Cora West (Box 83)
      - Fraser, James Earle, 17 glass negatives (Box 83, 84)
      - Fraser, Laura Gardin, 2 glass plate negatives (Oversize 23)
      - Gardin, Alice Tilton (Box 84)
      - Harding, Ann (Box 84)
      - Robinson, Edwin Arlington, 1872-1933 (Box 84)
  - Artifacts
    - Box covers, box covers from the James Earle Fraser Lantern Slide Collection, removed 9 Oct 1976 (Box 67)
  - Fraser Lantern Slide Collection
    "This procession of Great American Artists is presented by the National Academy of Design to create a better understanding of the Art of this country."
    - Architecture
      - Bacon, Henry (Lincoln Memorial), 14 slides (Oversize 24)
      - Goodhue, Bertram (Nebraska State Capitol), 4 slides (Oversize 24)
      - Goodhue, Bertram (Nebraska State Capitol), 4 slides (Oversize 24)
      - McKim, Charles (Boston Public Library, Morgan Library, Columbia Library), 10 slides (Oversize 24)
      - Towne, Eithal (Center Church, New Haven, CT), 1 slide (Oversize 24)
    - Painting
      - Abbey, Edwin Austin, 3 slides (Oversize 24)
      - Alexander, John, 5 slides (Oversize 24)
      - Bellows, George, 13 slides (Oversize 24)
      - Blakelock, Ralph, 5 slides (Oversize 24)
      - Blum, Robert, 2 slides (Oversize 24)
      - Cassatt, Mary, 9 slides (Oversize 24)
      - Chase, William, 8 slides (Oversize 24)
      - Copley, John Singleton, 10 slides (Oversize 24)
      - Davies, Arthur B., 32 slides (Oversize 24)
      - Durand, Asher B., 7 slides (Oversize 24)
      - Duveneck, Frank, 24 slides (Oversize 24)
      - Earins, Thomas, 14 slides (Oversize 24)
      - Earl, Ralph, 2 slides (Oversize 24)
      - Fuller, George, 8 slides (Oversize 24)
      - Harding, Chester, 10 slides (Oversize 24)
      - Henri, Robert, 13 slides (Oversize 24)
      - Hesselius, Gustavus, 3 slides (Oversize 24)
      - Homer, Winslow, 15 slides (Oversize 24)
      - Inman, Henry, 3 slides (Oversize 24)
      - Innes, George, 10 slides (Oversize 24)
      - Jarvis, John W., 6 slides (Oversize 24)
      - Lafarge, John, 2 slides (Oversize 24)
      - MacCameron, robert, 3 slides (Oversize 24)
      - Martin, Homer, 6 slides (Oversize 24)
      - Morse, Samuel F.B., 10 slides (Oversize 24)
      - Murphy, F.X., 7 slides (Oversize 24)
      - Murphy, J. Francis, 4 slides (Oversize 24)
      - Neagle, John, 4 slides (Oversize 24)
      - Peal, Charles Wilson, 6 slides (Oversize 24)
      - Peal, Rembrandt, 6 slides (Oversize 24)
      - Ryder, Albert P., 10 slides (Oversize 24)
      - Sargent, John Singer, 19 slides (Oversize 24)
      - Sharples, James, 1 slide (Oversize 24)
      - Stuart, Gilbert, 10 slides (Oversize 24)
      - Sully, Thomas, 9 slides (Oversize 24)
      - Thayer, Abbott, 25 slides (Oversize 24)
      - Trumball, John, 7 slides (Oversize 24)
      - Twachman, John, 11 slides (Oversize 24)
      - Tryon, Dwight William, 1 slide (Oversize 24)
      - Vedder, Elihu, 5 slides (Oversize 24)
      - Weir, J. Alden, 7 slides (Oversize 24)
      - West, Benjamin, 5 slides (Oversize 24)
      - Whistler, James McNeil, 13 slides (Oversize 24)
    - Prints, 3 slides (Oversize 24)
    - Sculpture
      - Bartlett, Paul, 2 slides (Oversize 24)
      - Borglum, Solon, 5 slides (Oversize 24)
      - French, Daniel Chester, 5 slides (Oversize 24)
      - Grafely, Charles, 4 slides (Oversize 24)
      - Saint Gaudens, Augustus, 2 slides (Oversize 24)
      - Ward, J.Q.A., 4 slides (Oversize 24)
    - Unidentified, 5 slides (Oversize 24)
    - Title Slides (with names and dates of artists), 40 slides (Oversize 24)
Index to Edwin Arlington Robinson materials
The collection contains considerable material relating to Edwin Arlington Robinson. For Robinson's correspondence, see Index to chronological correspondence below. To assist in locating non-correspondence material, the following index is provided.
Betts, Craven Langstroth: Verse, "To Edwin Arlington Robinson on His Fiftieth Birthday" Box 61
Book reviews, 1920-1935 Box 55
Ephemera, miscellaneous, 1904-1933 Box 55
Fraser, James Earle: Article, on Edwin Arlington Robinson, undated Box 61
Glass negatives, undated Box 84
Newspaper clippings Box 55
Obituaries, 1935 Box 55
Photographs Box 59 Oversize 3
Poetry, 1919 Box 55
Scrapbook, undated Oversize 5
Memorial plaque Box 36
Robinson, Edwin Arlington: Article, The First Seven Years, 1930 Box 66
Robinson, Edwin Arlington: Verse, "Cavender's House" Box 66
Robinson, Edwin Arlington: Verse, "Dionysus in Doubt", 1925 Box 66
Robinson, Edwin Arlington: Verse, "The Man Who Died Twice", 1922 Box 66
Sketches (of Robinson)Box 22 Box 50 Oversize 3 Oversize 9
Miscellaneous material, 1920-1965 Box 55
Index to chronological correspondence
Correspondence is indexed alphabetically by author's surname. The number of letters from a particular correspondent and the bracketing dates are given. Use the date to locate the letter in the chronological Correspondence [General] section (boxes 1-9). If the letter is filed elsewhere, the location is given as "filed under [xxx]." Recipients of letters are given where known. Abbreviations of frequently-used names are as follows:
JEF -- James Earle Fraser
LGF -- Laura Gardin Fraser
ATG -- Alice Tilton Gardin
EAR -- Edwin Arlington Robinson
Fraser -- indicates either James Earle or Laura Gardin Fraser
Acheson, Dean 1933 Jun 27 (1, to Fraser)
Acheson, Dean 1933 Jun 27 (1, to Fraser)
Adams, Herbert 1928 Aug-1940 Jun (5, to Fraser)
Albright, John Joseph 1924 Feb 11 (1, to Fraser)
Baldwin, Raymond 1944 May 5 (1, to Fraser)
Banks, Samuel J. 1926 Jul 31 (1, to EAR)
Beatty, Bessie 1944 Jun 7 (1, to Fraser)
Belmont, Eleanor (Mrs. August) 1937 Feb-1942 Mar (4, to Fraser)
Belmont, Perry 1929 Feb-1945 Oct (2, to Fraser)
Belmont, Perry 1926 Feb-1936 Jun (9, to Fraser) - filed under Business Records: Gallatin, Albert (Box 15)
Blashfield, Edwin H. 1929 May-1936 Sep (5, to Fraser)
Bostrom, Wollmar Filip 1929 Feb 14 (1, to Fraser)
Brooks, Van Wyck 1941 Spring-1953 Oct (3, to Fraser)
Buis, Jules 1928 Jun (1, EAR)
Calder, A. Stirling 1928 Jul 29 (2, to Fraser)
Case, Francis 1959 Nov-1960 Feb (2, to Fraser)
Cather, Willa 1927 Apr 19 (1, to Edith J.R. Isaacs)
Chindblom, Carl R. 1933 Feb-1933 Feb (2, to Fraser)
Collins, Mary Love 1932 Jul-1948 Jul (56, to Fraser)
Collins, Mary Love 1937 Mar 26 (1, to Ray Henderson)
Coolidge, Grace 1929 Apr-1950 Dec (10, to Fraser)
Crisp, Charles R. 1928 Jan 20 (1, to Fraser)
Curran, Charles C. 1924 Apr-1932 Apr (4, to Fraser)
Cross, Wilbur L. 1933 Mar 20 (1, to Fraser)
Darling, Jay N. 1922 Sep-1956 Jun (141, to Fraser) 1925 May 13 (1, to EAR)
Delano, William A. 1928 Aug-1953 Oct (3, to Fraser)
Delue, Donald 1950 Sep-1960 Sep (2, to Fraser)
Denys, Rev. F. Ward 1925 Feb-1925 Nov (3, toFraser) - filed under Business Records: Denys, Rev. F. Ward (Box 13)
Dunn, James C. 1949 Nov 17 (1, to Fraser )
Edison, Charles 1947 Sep 19 (1, to Fraser) - filed under Business Records: Edison, Thomas Alva, seated figure (Boxes 13, 14)
Edison, Mrs Thomas A. 1931 Apr 1 (1, to Fraser) - filed under Business Records: Edison, Thomas Alva, seated figure (Boxes 13, 14) n.d. (1, to Fraser)
Erskine, John 1927 Apr 20 (1, to Edith J.R. Isaacs)
Fackenthal, C. Frank 1929 Mar-1934 Oct (7, to Fraser)
Faulkner, Barry 1924 Nov-1953 Nov (10, to Fraser)
Finley, John H. 1930 Jul-1933 Jun (10, to Fraser)
Firestone, Harvey S. Jr. 1940 Dec-1953 Oct (6, to Fraser) - filed under Business Records: Firestone, Harvey S. Memorial (Box 14)
Flanagan, John 1928 Jul-1944 Jun (14, to Fraser)
Frazier, Kenneth 1927 Jul-1932 Jun (3, to Fraser)
French, Daniel Chester 1917 Jan-1931 Apr (18, to Fraser)
Gallatin, Albert 1929 Jan-1947 Dec (9, to Fraser) - filed under Business Records: Gallatin, Albert (Box 15)